https://www.circamax.com/privacy-policy.html

0 items in cart
Subtotal:
en / USD
Select regional settings:
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Heard and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
en / USD
Select regional settings:
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Heard and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
en / USD
Select regional settings:
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Heard and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyCircaMax a division of Circa Enterprises Inc., respects an individual's right to privacy and to the protection of his or her personal information. This Privacy Policy incorporates the provisions of the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act of Canada and the Personal Information Protection Act of Alberta.
AccountabilityCircaMax a division of Circa Enterprises Inc. is responsible for control and use of the personal information which it collects.
Purpose for Collection, Use and DisclosurePersonal information collected from customers and prospective customers, and employees of customers and prospective customers, is used solely for the purpose of communicating with and providing goods and services to that customer or prospective customer, including processing payments for such goods and services.
ConsentImplied consent to use, as identified above, is assumed when individuals provide personal information to CircaMax a division of Circa Enterprises Inc., Personal information provided for any other purpose is on an opt-in basis.
Limiting CollectionCircaMax collects and maintains personal information only as necessary for the uses identified above.
Limiting Use, Disclosure and RetentionPersonal information is used only for the purposes identified above and is not disclosed outside the company without the written consent of the individual, except as required by law. It is retained only as long as is necessary to fulfill these purposes, or as required by law.
AccuracyCircaMax a division of Circa Enterprises Inc., takes all reasonable measures to ensure personal information collected is accurate. This, however, is dependent on individuals providing accurate information. Any errors or omissions are corrected as they are identified.
SafeguardsCircaMax a division of Circa Enterprises Inc., uses reasonable and appropriate security safeguards to protect personal information from loss, misuse, alteration and unauthorized access. These include physical, administrative and electronic security measures.
Access to personal information is restricted to those employees requiring access to perform their job responsibilities. Employees requiring such access are trained on and are required to abide by this Privacy Policy.
Individual AccessIndividuals have the right to access their personal information retained by CircaMax a division of Circa Enterprises Inc., and to know for what purpose this information is being used. To obtain such access contact the Manager responsible for that particular information, if known, or the ACC Privacy Coordinator.
If you have a question or complaint regarding this policy or our  privacy practices contact us at 1-800-661-8564.
Sign up for CircaMax news
Subscribe
Can't subscribe you right now. Try later
Thank you for subscribing to the newsletter! We hope you enjoy shopping at CircaMax
© 2016 - 2020 CircaMax. All rights reserved.
Powered by X-Cart online shop software
